const questionsEng = [
  {
    id: 0,
    question: "What year was League of Legends released?",
    answers: ["2006", "2008", "2009", "2011"],
    correct: 2,
  },
  {
    id: 1,
    question: "Which game has more average online players?",
    answers: ["Dota 2", "League of Legends"],
    correct: 1,
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question: "How long was the longest official League of Legends game?",
    answers: [
      "from 70 to 80 minutes",
      "from 81 to 90 minutes",
      "from 91 to 100 minutes",
      "more than 101 minutes",
    ],
    correct: 2,
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question:
      "How many champions have been released in League of Legends? (on 01/22/2025)",
    answers: ["161", "163", "164", "168"],
    correct: 3,
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question:
      "How many territories are there in the world of League of Legends?",
    answers: ["8", "10", "11", "13"],
    correct: 3,
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question: "What territory is the Malphite champion from?",
    answers: ["Ishtal", "Ionia", "Demacia", "Targon"],
    correct: 0,
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question: "What territory is the Kog'Maw champion from?",
    answers: ["Ionia", "Abyss", "Shadow Islands", "Targon"],
    correct: 1,
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question:
      "Which team won the League of Legends World Championship 2024 (also known as LoL Worlds 2024 or just Worlds 2024)?",
    answers: ["T1", "Weibo Gaming", "Bilibili Gaming", "JD Gaming"],
    correct: 0,
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question: "What is this League of Legends streamer's nickname?",
    answers: ["Thebausffs", "Tyler1", "Nemesis", "Jankos"],
    correct: 1,
    img: "https://flic.kr/p/2nXfqor",
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question: "Who is the Emperor of Shurima?",
    answers: ["Renekton", "K'Sante", "Azir", "Amumu"],
    correct: 2,
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question: "Who is Orn's brother?",
    answers: ["Volibir", "Braum", "Gnar", "Olaf"],
    correct: 0,
  },
];

export default questionsEng;
